谢了 老兄
Thanks, mate.
♪ But when I picture you  I'm intense
♪ I lose myself inside you like a maze
♪ I'm waiting to... ♪
又开始吸烟了？
Back on the smokes?
是啊
Yeah.
找到那孩子了吗？
You find the kid?
找到了
Mm.
那就好
- That's good.
你不能在这儿工作了  兄弟
You can't work here no more, mate.
你家里的事 我很抱歉
Sorry about all that shit with your family.
嗯 我也很抱歉
Yeah, so am I.
没事的 兄弟
It's all right, bub.
没事的
It's all right.
- 你还好吗   - 你好
- How you going?  - Hi.
抱歉 那天吓到你了
Sorry for scaring you the other day.
不是有意的
Didn't mean to.
你还想过来吗
You still want to come over?
确定吗
You sure?
百分百确定？
100% sure?
我想要一个虎皮鹦鹉
I want a budgie.
- 虎皮鹦鹉     - 是的
- A budgie?  - Yeah.
可以吗
Can we have a budgie?
你要虎皮鹦鹉干嘛
What do you want a budgie for?
因为很可爱啊
- Because they're cute. - Mm.
好的  我尽量
Yeah, we'll see.
- 要吃的吗  - 不用 谢谢
- You want something to eat? - No, thanks.
- 布利特  - 你好
- Britt.    - Hi.
有没有新鲜事？
What's news?
没有
Nothing.
最近有写新的笑话吗
So have you written any more jokes?
没有 我不想做脱口秀了
No. I don't want to be a stand-up comedian anymore.
- 为什么呢  - 我想做演员
- How come? - I want to be an actress.
演员啊
An actress?
工资会更高一点
Yeah. It pays better.
好吧  如果你擅长这个  是的
Well, if you're good at it, yeah.
学校里要演罗密欧与朱丽叶的戏剧
At school we're doing aRomeo and Juliet play,
我想去演朱丽叶
and I want to audition for Juliet.
- 罗密欧与朱丽叶？  - 是的
- Romeo and Juliet, hey? - Yeah.
哦  那很好
Oh, that's cool.
Hey 布利特
Hey, Britt.
你知道这是谁吗
Do you know who this is?
不
No.
这是你爷爷
This is your grandpa.
你好 布列塔尼
Hello, Brittany.
- 嗨   - 你好吗
- Hi.   - How are you?
我很好
I'm good.
很高兴见到你
I'm so pleased to meet you.
我也是
- Me too.  - Well...
我都不知道我有一个爷爷
I didn't know I had a grandpa.
我们要再来一次吗
are we gonna have a rematch?
当然
- Of course.
你可以和他玩
And you can play.
好
Right.
- 那我们玩什么  - 抽积木
- What are we playing? - Jenga.
你还好吗  儿子
How are you, son?
去里面  布利特
Go inside, Britt.
- 为什么   -进去吧
- Why?    - Just go in the house.
坐下   坐
Sit down. Sit. Sit.
好狗
Good dog.
坐下  兄弟
Cheers, mate. Mm.
出来吗
You out?
你呢
Are you?
嗯
Yeah.
让我看一下？
You want to show me?
- 看看你的   - 好
- Let's see yours. - All right.
你这狗娘养的还真的难搞
Tough little cunt, aren't you?
你这个混蛋
Yeah, you fucker!
你他妈的
Oh, you fuck.
眼睛不错
Nice eye.
脸挺好看
Nice face.
继续
Come on.
-嗨   - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hey.
你来了  总统先生
There he is. El presidente.
发生什么事了？
What's going on?
我有文尼的消息了
Oh, I got a tip-off about Vinnie.
都是些胡说八道的假消息
Now, it could be all bullshit,
我知道名字
but I got a name.
叫什么
Who?
雷 虚休
Ray Sh-Shoes...
雷·修斯特林
Ray Shoestring?
-雷·修斯特林
Ray Shoestring.
- 雷·修斯特林   - 是的
- Ray Shoestring.  - Yeah.
有听说过这个人吗
You ever heard of him?
没有印象
Doesn't ring any bells.
谁告诉你的
Who gave you the tip?
不知道   接到一个电话
I don't know. Just a phone call.
所以 你打算怎么做
So what you want to do?
不知道
Don't know.
打电话问问吧
I'll make some calls, ask around, eh?
那好吧
Yeah, right.
需要我查一查吗
Do you want me to look into it?
不用了  我来处理
Nah, I'll take care of it.
我猜你他妈的保准会
I'll bet you fucking will.
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
干得不错 雷
Well done, Ray.
你来开车吗
So you want to drive?
好的
Yeah.
-我要问你一个问题    - 嗯
- Let me ask you a question. - Mm.
- 文尼  - 怎么了
- Vinnie.  - Mm.
死得很快吗
Was that quick?
嗯
Yeah.
很好
Good.
我们走
Let's go.
走
Come on.
你想干什么？
So, what do youse want?
我想要你的命
Well, I want you to die.
我是说你要多少钱
I mean how much do you want?
要多少钱？
How much do we want for what?
才能放了我
To let me slide.
操  我不知道
Shit, I don't know.
你想要多少 雷
How much do you want, Raymond?
我不知道
I don't know, man.
你有多少钱
How much you got?
差不多 65万
$650K, give or take.
-  真的吗  -  嗯
- Really?   - Yeah.
- 在哪里   - 埋起来了
- Where?  - It's buried.
装满了四个行李袋
four duffel bags, filled to the brim.
都是干净的钱
All clean.
- 你在干什么？   - 65万  怎么分？
- What are you doing? - So what's that split between two?
- 是多少?
... what is that?
32万吗
323...
是32.5万
It's 325.
-  你在干什么    - 32.5万
- What are you doing? - 25.
32.5万
325 grand.
你很满意 对吗 雷
You happy with that, Ray?
不是很满意
Not particularly.
32.5万  你还不满意？
You're not happy with $325,000?
通常来说 我会满意 但是
Well, normally, I would be, mate, but, uh,
你的人杀了我的狗
your guys killed my fucking dog.
好吧  我很抱歉
Okay, I am sorry about that.
我没叫他们这么做  我也有一只狗
I didn't tell 'em to do it. I have a dog.
- 我喜欢狗   - 抱歉就好 伙计
- I love dogs. - As long as you're sorry, mate.
真的对不起
I am sorry. I mean that. I do.
所以  钱在哪里
So where's this money?
- 在马鲁塔  - 马鲁塔的哪里
- Maroota. - Where in Maroota?
我怎么知道你会让我走
How do I know you're gonna let me go?
因为我们说了 会放你走
'Cause we're just telling you we'll let you go.
光凭一句话可不行
Well, I need a bit more than that.
哦  是吗？ 你知道吗？
Oh, do you? You know what,
- 去他的   - 啊  啊  啊  啊  啊
- fuck this.  - Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
- 别开枪  - 为什么不
- Don't shoot him. - Why not?
把他扔进水里吧  伙计
Just throw him in the water, mate.
所以我把他的脚给拷上了
That's why I put the bloody cuffs on his ankles.
对  所以我们…
Right. So we just...
我们只是淹死这小妞
we just drown the cunt.
把他推进去
Push him in.
钱在哪里
Where's the money?
我怎么知道你不会杀我？
Well... how do I know you're not gonna kill me here?
哦  操 我们在兜圈子
Oh, fuck. We're going around in circles.
你想怎么办？
What do you want to do?
那是一大笔钱
That's a lot of money.
伙计  我们怎么做？
Mate, what do you want us to do?
嗯  我想...
Well, I got...
我只是不能相信你的话  雷
I just can't take your word for it, Ray.
好吧  我们只能口头答应你 如果你不相信我们
Well, that's all we got, mate.So if you don't believe us,
我不知道该他妈的告诉你什么
I don't know what to fucking tell you.
好的   这个怎么样？
Okay. How about this?
我们一起去马鲁塔· 怎么样？
We go to Maroota, right?
- 好 好 好  - 嗯 很好
- Right, right? Good. - Yeah. Yes. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
我们先去那里
So, we get there, yeah?
到了之后你停好车  我下车
When we get there, you park the car.
我们都下车
I get out.
- 你们这些人... 我们都下了车    - 操
- You guys... We all get out of the car.  - Fuck me.
我留在车里  给你们指个方向
I stay at the car. I point you in the direction
告诉你们钱在哪里
of-of-of where the money is,
你们 走过去  拿
and you guys-you guys-you guys walk over, you go get it.
然后呢
And then what?
然后 你们到了之后
Then, when you get to the spot,
然后我  --  我就离开
then I'll-I'll start walking off.
我们看起来像一对傻子吗？
Do we look like a couple of fuckwits?
-好吧
- Hmm? - Okay.
你到了那里  你把它挖出来
How about you get there, you dig it up.
这笔钱... 钱在一个袋子里
The money's... the money's in a bag, yeah?
你把袋子挖出来
You dig up the bag.
- 你们拿到袋子之后  - 这样吧
- You get the bags...- You-you know what,
这是不可能发生的
this is what's fucking gonna happen.
我们留在车旁边
All right? We'll stay by the car.
你知道钱在哪里  所以  你慢慢走过去
You know where the money is, so you can toddle off
然后把袋子挖出来
and you dig up the bags.
- 好吗？   - 好
- Right?  - Yeah.
- 是的     - 是吗？
- Yes.      - Yeah?
- 是的  - 是的     - 是吗？
- Yeah. Yeah.      - Yeah?
- 我们能走了吗  -是的   我们... 是的
- Can we go?    - Yeah. We... Yeah.
我们呆在车里
We stay at the car.
还是不行
That's not gonna work either.
为什么？
Why?
如果他在某一个袋子里放了枪怎么办
What if he's got a fucking gun in one of the bags?
操
Oh, fuck.
好吧  要不 这样
All right, here's what's gonna happen, all right?
我们呆在车里
We stay at the car.
- 我和他待在车上 你出去    - 不  不  不
- You go back out there...- No, no, no.
- 不  他呆在车边    - 好的
- No, he stays by the car.  - Okay.
你留下来... 他留在车旁边
You stay... He stays by the car.
我知道我要说的是什么
I know what I meant to say, right?
我知道我想说的是什么   他留在车旁边
I know what I meant to say.  He stays by the car.
- 嗯  - 对吗？ 我们去那里
- Mm. - Right? We go out there
然后我们把袋子挖出来  对吗？
and we dig up the bags, right?
确保钱都在那里
Make sure the money's all there.
然后我给你一个信号  对吗？
And then I'll give you a signal, right?
确保一切顺利   然后...
Make sure everything's okay. And then...
然后  他就
and then, only then...
可以走了
he can go.
- 好  - 好吧
- Yeah.  - Okay.
那是...那是... 是吗？
Is that-is that... Yeah?
- 就这样了   是的   - 一个信号
- That's it. Yeah.  - S-Signal?
- 是的     - 好的
- Yeah.    - Okay.
高兴吗？
- Yeah. - We happy?
那  我们现在去马鲁塔  走
- Well, let's go to Maroota.  - Let's go.
你
Oh, you...
你进去
In you go.
我不想让你们听到我鬼叫
I don't want to sound like a pain in the ass,
我能跟你们一起坐在车里吗
but can I just ride in the car with you guys?
当然不行
Absolutely not.
我有幽闭恐怖症
Come on. I suffer from claustrophobia.
你不进去的话
You're gonna suffer from lead poisoning
你就会铅中毒
if you don't fucking get in there.
操
Fuck.
进去
Come on.
还好吗
- You all right?
注意手
Watch your fingers.